<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Caleb Mullan's Site</title><link>//bemuseed.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Caleb Mullan's Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 01:08:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//bemuseed.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating Novel Art Styles With AI</title><link>//bemuseed.github.io/posts/novelartstyleswithai/novelartstyleswithai.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 01:08:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>//bemuseed.github.io/posts/novelartstyleswithai/novelartstyleswithai.html</guid><description>The goal of this project is to enable the creation of new, appealing art-styles with AI. The method used to attempt this is training Stable Diffusion LoRa models on specific art styles, then iteratively merging these into new models and comparing their differences mathematically. The training is achieved by preparing a standard set of images, then using ControlNet to &amp;lsquo;convert&amp;rsquo; them into an artist&amp;rsquo;s style.
The project currently consists of a method of training styled LoRa&amp;rsquo;s, and an interactive program that combines and analyses them.</description></item><item><title>A guide to mathematically comparing Stable Diffusion models</title><link>//bemuseed.github.io/posts/flattening-unflattening-stable-diffusion-models/flattening-unflattening-stable-diffusion-models.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 10:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>//bemuseed.github.io/posts/flattening-unflattening-stable-diffusion-models/flattening-unflattening-stable-diffusion-models.html</guid><description>Introduction A Stable Diffusion model, whether a complete copy or a LoRa, is just a Pytorch model - and a Pytorch model like any neural net, is just a series of floating point numbers. These are contained within tensors, a form of array, and most models exist as a list of tensors of varying shapes, sizes, and dimensions. Being able to compare them is useful for any form of statistical analysis, or just calculating useful metrics like average difference of values, like we will here.</description></item></channel></rss>