<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Caleb Mullan's Site</title><link>//bemuseed.github.io/posts.html</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Caleb Mullan's Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 01:08:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//bemuseed.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating Novel Art Styles With AI</title><link>//bemuseed.github.io/posts/novelartstyleswithai/novelartstyleswithai.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 01:08:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>//bemuseed.github.io/posts/novelartstyleswithai/novelartstyleswithai.html</guid><description>The goal of this project is to enable the creation of new, appealing art-styles with AI. This is to be done by manipulating Stable Diffusion models trained on pre-existing, specific styles. The aim is that we&amp;rsquo;ll be able to move around the &amp;lsquo;space&amp;rsquo; of all such models, using both model merging and Principal Component Analysis.
Fine-tuning a model with Dreambooth using Google Colab Dreambooth allows a Stable Diffusion model to be further trained upon a particular subject (a character or art-style).</description></item><item><title>A guide to flattening and unflattening Pytorch models</title><link>//bemuseed.github.io/posts/flattening-unflattening-stable-diffusion-models/flattening-unflattening-stable-diffusion-models.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 10:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>//bemuseed.github.io/posts/flattening-unflattening-stable-diffusion-models/flattening-unflattening-stable-diffusion-models.html</guid><description>Introduction A Pytorch model, like any neural net, is essentially a series of floating point numbers. These are contained within tensors, a form of array, and most models exist as a list of tensors of varying shapes, sizes, and dimensions. This makes mathematical operations on these numbers more difficult, like calculating an average model or performing mutations using techniques like Principal Component Analysis. Even just for comparing models side-by-side, &amp;lsquo;flattening&amp;rsquo; them is useful.</description></item><item><title>My First Post</title><link>//bemuseed.github.io/posts/my-first-post.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 23:54:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>//bemuseed.github.io/posts/my-first-post.html</guid><description>My first post!</description></item></channel></rss>